[{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440075,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":26803,"timeElapsed":224879},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980475492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":35414,"timeElapsed":260296},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7380,"timeElapsed":267680},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490243,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":7364,"timeElapsed":275047},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980495826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":5580,"timeElapsed":280630},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980509574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":13744,"timeElapsed":294378},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980526375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":16798,"timeElapsed":311179},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":11215,"timeElapsed":322395},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6966,"timeElapsed":329364},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":8114,"timeElapsed":339214},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980560057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5644,"timeElapsed":344861},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568743,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":8683,"timeElapsed":353547},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":9748,"timeElapsed":363297},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980584709,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6214,"timeElapsed":369513},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980590376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5665,"timeElapsed":375180},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980597259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":6881,"timeElapsed":382063},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980602477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":5215,"timeElapsed":387281},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980606409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3929,"timeElapsed":391212},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980612928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6516,"timeElapsed":397732},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980648791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":34277,"timeElapsed":433595},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5332,"timeElapsed":438929},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6630,"timeElapsed":445561},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3948,"timeElapsed":449512},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3600,"timeElapsed":453115},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980672443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4128,"timeElapsed":457246},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980676624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4179,"timeElapsed":461427},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980683729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":7103,"timeElapsed":468532},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980687944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4210,"timeElapsed":472747},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692027,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4080,"timeElapsed":476831},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980716976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":23382,"timeElapsed":501780},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980721592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4614,"timeElapsed":506396},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980728739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7145,"timeElapsed":513543},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980733524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4783,"timeElapsed":518328},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980736660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3134,"timeElapsed":521464},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3963,"timeElapsed":525430},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980748808,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8180,"timeElapsed":533612},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980758876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":10065,"timeElapsed":543679},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980762122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3245,"timeElapsed":546926},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980889458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":125832,"timeElapsed":674262},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980894289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4829,"timeElapsed":679093},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980901059,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":6768,"timeElapsed":685863},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980905945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4883,"timeElapsed":690749},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980909775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3828,"timeElapsed":694579},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980913791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4015,"timeElapsed":698595},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980916462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2668,"timeElapsed":701265},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980923476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":7012,"timeElapsed":708280},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980929793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":6314,"timeElapsed":714597},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980957825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":26512,"timeElapsed":742629},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980963927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":6100,"timeElapsed":748731},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980967425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3495,"timeElapsed":752229},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980971359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3932,"timeElapsed":756163},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980974544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3182,"timeElapsed":759347},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980977993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3447,"timeElapsed":762797},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980981177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3182,"timeElapsed":765981},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980986974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5795,"timeElapsed":771778},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980989943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2967,"timeElapsed":774747},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981010126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":18597,"timeElapsed":794930},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981014494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4365,"timeElapsed":799298},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981021760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7263,"timeElapsed":806564},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981024859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3097,"timeElapsed":809663},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981028042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3180,"timeElapsed":812846},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981031458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":3414,"timeElapsed":816262},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981034344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2883,"timeElapsed":819148},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981038427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4081,"timeElapsed":823231},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981042212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3783,"timeElapsed":827016},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981060712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":16950,"timeElapsed":845516},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981064106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3393,"timeElapsed":848910},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981070058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5951,"timeElapsed":854862},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981075493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5433,"timeElapsed":860297},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981079742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4247,"timeElapsed":864546},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981093144,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":13399,"timeElapsed":877948},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981096944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3798,"timeElapsed":881748},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981102078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5131,"timeElapsed":886882},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981105594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3513,"timeElapsed":890398},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981133794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":26750,"timeElapsed":918598},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981137344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3546,"timeElapsed":922148},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981141127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3781,"timeElapsed":925931},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981145559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4429,"timeElapsed":930363},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981148994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3432,"timeElapsed":933798},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981154243,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5246,"timeElapsed":939047},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981159944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":5699,"timeElapsed":944748},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981168944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8997,"timeElapsed":953748},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981172377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3430,"timeElapsed":957180},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981182074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":7396,"timeElapsed":966878},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981186007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3931,"timeElapsed":970811},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981191244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5235,"timeElapsed":976048},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981209744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":18497,"timeElapsed":994547},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981213793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4047,"timeElapsed":998597},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981217809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":4014,"timeElapsed":1002613},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981221313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3501,"timeElapsed":1006117},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981225424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4110,"timeElapsed":1010228},{"subjectID":"ug34ouzsqp","prolificID":"6658c1d8934ec07966372945","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2690fdc5fcf05fba6fe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981228879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3452,"timeElapsed":1013682}]